<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
 
5724-Q55

(c) Copyright IBM Corp. 2009, 2011  All Rights Reserved.

US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure
restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->
<cheatsheet title="Running the Rapid Generator wizard">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This cheat sheet shows you how to generate jobs from a physical data model.
         <br/>
         This cheat sheet assumes that a Rapid Generator configuration and a physical
         data model containing SAP table metadata exist.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item dialog="true"
         title="Open the Rapid Generator wizard">
      <description>      
      In the main toolbar select <b>SAP Pack -> Generate Data Stage jobs</b>.
      The Rapid Generator wizard will open.
      
      </description>
      <action required="false"
			pluginId="com.ibm.is.sappack.gen.tools.jobgenerator"
			class="com.ibm.iis.sappack.gen.tools.jobgenerator.jobgenwizard.JobgeneratorCheatSheetAction"/>   

   </item>
   <item title="Select Rapid generator configuration">
      <description>
      On the first wizard page you select the Rapid generator configuration and the physical
      data model(s) which constitute the source and / or target model.
      <br/>
      Select the Rapid Generator configuration created previously and the physical data model
      containing the SAP logical tables.
      <br/>
      Click <b>Next</b>.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Select object types">
     <description>
     On this page you can
     select the type of object in the physical data model you want to generate jobs for.
     The checkboxes are enabled if the configuration type supports the types and if
     one object of that type exists in the model.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Select Tables -> Data Tables.
     <br/>
     Click <b>Next</b>. 
     </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Select ABAP extract settings">
      <description>
      On this page you can specify settings for the ABAP extract stages to be generated.
      <br/>
      <br/>
      Leave all defaults and check "Save ABAP programs to workspace".
      <br/>
      Click <b>Next</b>. 
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Information Server details">
      <description>
      This page lets you select the Information Server connection, DataStage project, and
      folder where the jobs should be generated. 
      <br/>
      Note that the connection is defined in the
      SAP Pack Connections view 
      (see separate cheat sheet "Defining connections to SAP systems and Information Server instances").
      <br/>
      <br/>
      Select the Information Server connection first and select the project and folder.
      <br/>
      Click <b>Next</b>. 
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Finish the wizard">
      <description>
      Review the information on the summary page.
         <br/>
         Click <b>Finish</b> to start the job generation.
         <br/>
         If you choose to let the job generation run in background, open the "Progress" view to get updates
         on the status. Once job generation is finished, you can click on the link there to view the results.
      </description>
      <onCompletion>Congratulations! You have successfully initiated job generation.
      </onCompletion>
         </item>
      </cheatsheet>
