<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
 
5724-Q55

(c) Copyright IBM Corp. 2012  All Rights Reserved.

US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure
restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->
<cheatsheet title="Defining connections to SAP systems and Information Server instances">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This cheat sheet shows you how to define connections to SAP systems and / or Information Server instances. 
         If your Information Server instance has SAP connections defined (created with, e.g.,  the DataStage Administrator for SAP)
         you can re-use these connections in Rapid Modeler and Rapid Generator. 
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         title="Open the SAP Pack Connections View">
         
      <description>
      In the main toolbar, go
 to <b>Window</b> &gt; <b>Show View</b> &gt; <b>Other</b>. Search
      for the category <b>InfoSphere for SAP</b> and select <b>SAP Pack connections</b>.
      <br/>
      Click <b>OK</b>.
      </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.views.showView(org.eclipse.ui.views.showView.viewId=com.ibm.iis.sappack.gen.common.ui.connectionsView)"/>   </item>
   <item
         title="Determine the connection type">
      <description>
         The SAP Pack Connections View offers two ways of creating connections to SAP systems:
         <br/>
         1. <b>Local</b>: This is a connection that is only known in your workspace. This is 
         the best choice if you don't work with Information Server.
         <br/>
         2. <b>Information Server connection</b>: If you have an Information Server somewhere in your
         environment and you have SAP connections defined there (e.g. with the DataStage Administrator for SAP
         tool of the DataStage components of the SAP Packs) you can re-use these connections here.
         This is typically the best choice if you work with Conversion Workbench for SAP.
         <br/>
         The next two steps describe in detail how connections are created for these connection types.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         skip="true"
         title="Create a local SAP connection">
      <description>      
      In the SAP Pack connections view, right click on <b>Local SAP Connections</b> and select <b>New...</b>.
      Enter all necessary information in the panel that opens and click <b>OK</b> to save.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item skip="true"
         title="Create an Information Server connection">
      <description>      
      In the SAP Pack connections view, right click on <b>Information Server Connections</b> and select <b>New...</b>.
      Enter all necessary information in the panel that opens and click <b>OK</b> to save.
      <br/>
      If you expand the Information Server connection in the view, you will see all SAP connections
      defined on this Information Server instance under the folder <b>DataStage SAP Connections</b>.
      </description>

   </item>
</cheatsheet>
