<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
 
5724-Q55

(c) Copyright IBM Corp. 2012  All Rights Reserved.

US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure
restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->
<cheatsheet title="Creating an ABAP Table List">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This cheat sheet shows you how to create a so-called ABAP table list. An ABAP Table List 
         contains a list of ABAP table (or logical table) names that can is used later on to define
         which tables are to be imported into a logical data model.
         <br/>
         <b>NOTE: Be sure to enter the names of projects, models, etc. in the following steps exactly as
         indicated otherwise the "Click to perform" buttons might not work. 
         However, the "Click when complete" buttons will continue to work.
         </b>
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         title="Open the Data perspective">
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective(org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective.perspectiveId=com.ibm.datatools.core.internal.ui.perspective)"/>
         
      <description>
         If you&apos;re not already in the Data perspective, in the main menu select <b>Window</b> &gt; <b>Open Perspective</b> &gt; <b>Data</b>.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Create a Data Design project">
      <description>      
      ABAP Table Lists must reside in a Data Design project.
      To create such a project, click on <b>File</b> &gt; <b>New</b> &gt; <b>Data Design Project</b>. 
         <br/>
         Enter <b>RMTestProject</b> in the <b>Project name</b> field.
         <br/>Click <b>Finish</b>.
      </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.newWizard(newWizardId=com.ibm.datatools.core.internal.ui.wizard.DatabaseCreationProjectWizard)"/>
   </item>
   <item dialog="true"
         title="Start the ABAP Table list creation wizard">
      <description>      
         Now, we are ready to create the ABAP Table List.
         In the main toolbar, click on <b>File</b> &gt; <b>New</b>  &gt; <b>Other</b> &gt;
         <b>InfoSphere Pack for SAP</b> &gt; <b>ABAP Table List</b>. 
      </description>
      <command
            required="true"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.newWizard(newWizardId=com.ibm.iis.sappack.gen.tools.sap.newTableListWizard)"/>

   </item>
   <item dialog="true" 
            title="Select creation options">
        <description>
        This page lets you select a Data Design Project where the ABAP Table List is to be created
        ant its name.
        <br/>
        Select the Data Design Project created previously (e.g., <b>RMTestProject</b>) 
        and choose a name (e.g., <b>ExampleTableList</b>).
        <br/>Click <b>Finish</b>.
        </description>
      </item>
   <item
         title="Define tables">
      <description>
         After finishing the creation wizard, the ABAP Table List editor is opened automatically. 
      To open the ABAP Table List at a later time, go to the file in the Data Project Explorer and double click on it.
         <br/>     
         The ABAP Table List editor consists of two tabs: 
         <br/>
         <br/><b>General</b>: This tab contains read-only and modifiable information like the file name, documentation, author, etc.
         <br/>
         <br/><b>Tables</b>: On this tab you can enter the names of the tables to be imported. Simply type in the table names, separated with commas and / or newlines
         into the <b>Tables</b> text field. If the field is empty or incorrect you will see a little red marker.
         Hovering over the marker will show you the type of error message as a tooltip. You can also search for tables directly on an SAP system by clicking the <b>Browse SAP</b>
         button.
         <br/><br/>
         Enter the table name <b>KNA1</b> in the <b>Tables</b> field.
         <br/>
         Save the file by typing <b>Ctrl + s</b>. 
      </description>
      <onCompletion>Congratulations! You have successfully created your first ABAP table list.
      </onCompletion>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
