<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
 
5724-Q55

(c) Copyright IBM Corp. 2012  All Rights Reserved.

US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure
restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->
<cheatsheet title="Using the new SAP Packs views">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This cheat sheet shows you how to use the new views introduced with this version of Rapid Modeler.
         These views will help you to organize your workspace and to analyze which metadata 
         was imported how.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         skip="true"
         title="The SAP Packs Navigator">
         
      <description>
      The SAP Packs Navigator presents a view on your workspace that focuses on the artifacts needed
      for Rapid Modeler and Rapid Generator.
      It shows all Data Design projects at the toplevel and newly introduced categories beneath them
      which, in turn, will contain the respective workspace objects.
      These categories are:
      <br/>
      - <b>Data models</b> with subcategories <b>Logical data models</b> and <b>Physical data models</b>.
      <br/>
      - <b>Rapid Modeler</b> with subcategories <b>Rapid Modeler configurations</b> and <b>SAP Object list</b>.
      The latter has, in turn, subcategories <b>ABAP Table Lists</b> and <b>IDoc Segment Lists</b>.
      <br/>
      <br/>
       
      </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.views.showView(org.eclipse.ui.views.showView.viewId=com.ibm.iis.sappack.gen.common.ui.sappacknavigator)"/>   
   </item>
   <item skip="true" 
         title="The SAP Import History View">
      <description>
      <b>Note: This feature is experimental and might be subject to change at any time.</b>
      <br/>
      <br/>
      The SAP Import History View shows you which objects you have used for metadata import 
      at any previous point in time. For instance, for a given logical data model, it can show you
      which metadata import runs were performed on this model. Or it can show you which ABAP Table List
      was used for which imports into which models. Another example is that it can show you which 
      SAP connection was used for which imports.
      <br/>
  
      It works as follows: 
      <br/>
      - Right-click on the object you are interested in in any applicable
      view (e.g. SAP Packs Navigator, Data Project Explorer, SAP Connections).
      <br/>
      - Select <b>InfoSphere Pack for SAP -> Show in SAP Import History View</b>.
      <br/>
      - The view will open and a tree structure will show the dependencies.
      <br/>
      - Use the <b>Up</b> and <b>Down</b> buttons to see upward or downward dependencies, respectively.
      <br/>
      - If you are interested in another object in the dependency tree, right-click on it and select
      <b>Focus On '...'</b>
         </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.views.showView(org.eclipse.ui.views.showView.viewId=com.ibm.is.sappack.gen.tools.sap.dependencyView)"/>   

   </item>
</cheatsheet>
